The story of two bands, one girl and a night they will never forget.
Spike Island is a comedy, drama, music film directed by Mat Whitecross.
Teenage musicians travel to England's Spike Island in the hope of attending an
outdoor performance by their favorite band, the Stone Roses.
Tits, played by Elliott Tittensor.
Sally, played by Emilia Clarke.
Dodge, played by Nico Mirallegro.
Little Gaz, played by Adam Long.
Zippy, played by Jordan Murphy.
Penfold, played by Oliver Heald.
Spike Island is a 2012 British comedy film directed by Mat
Whitecross and written by Chris Coghill.
It was distributed by Universal Pictures and Vertigo Films
and produced by Revolver Entertainment.
The film is based on the Stone Roses' seminal gig on Spike Island in Widnes, Cheshire, England, and follows the story of a group of friends who
idolise the band and try to get into the gig, but are faced with problems because they don't have tickets or a way to get there.
Spike Island premiered on 11 October 2012 at the BFI London Film
Festival and was released on DVD on 21 June 2013.
The film explores themes of ecstasy, liverpool, england,
cannabis, pot smoking, music business.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.